<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<artifacts_collection>
  <collection_info>
    <id>UC</id>
    <name>eTOUR Source Artifacts</name>
    <version>1.1</version>
    <description>Use cases</description>
  </collection_info>
  <artifacts>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC1</id>
      <content>Use case name ELIMINABENECULTURALE 
Delete a cultural object in the system. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. View the list of BeniCulturali as a result of the use case RicercaBeneCulturale, it selects and activates a function of elimination. 
2 Asks confirmation. 
3 Confirm the operation. 
4 Delete the cultural choice. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the successful elimination of the cultural. 
- Operator Agency cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
The system requirements blocks of input controls on receipt of confirmation of cancellation to avoid multiple submissions before the end of the operation.</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC10</id>
      <content>Use case name VISUALIZZASCHEDAPUNTODIRISTORO 
View the details of a selected point of rest. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. View the list of points of rest as a result of the use case RicercaPuntoDiRistoro, it selects and activates a function to view the card. 
2 Upload data to a selected restaurant. 
Exit conditions - The system displays the details of the selected point of rest. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC11</id>
      <content>Use case name VISUALIZZASTORICOCONVENZIONI 
View the history of conventions derived from a selected point of rest. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The Agency is in the form of a designated point of rest. 

Flow of events User System 
1. Access the features on the display of historical conventions. 
2 Upload data on conventions from the restaurant selected. 
Exit conditions - The system displays the history of conventions concerning the point of eating selected. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC12</id>
      <content>Use case name VISUALIZZASCHEDATURISTA 
View the details of a selected account Turista. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Tourists from the list obtained by activating the use case RicercaTurista will select and activate a function for displaying the card. 
2 Upload data to the selected account. 
Exit conditions - The system displays the card's Tourist selected. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC13</id>
      <content>Use case name ACTIVE / DISATTIVAACCOUNTTURISTA 
Enable or disable the account of a tourist. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The Agency is in the form of a tourist. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Activate the feature for the activation / deactivation by a given sheet tourist. 
2 Asks for confirmation of activation / deactivation. 
3 Confirm the operation. 
4 Enable / disable the account of the visitor you selected. 
Exit conditions - The notification of the outcome. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC14</id>
      <content>Use case name RICERCATURISTA 
Returns the list of tourist account in the system according to certain parameters. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Access the search functionality of a tourist. 
2 Show the form. 
3 Fill out the form and submit. 
4 Processing the request. 
Exit conditions - The system returns a list of accounts that meet Turista your search criteria. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC15</id>
      <content>Use case name MODIFICADATIACCOUNTTURISTA 
Change data of a selected account Turista. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Tourists from the list obtained by activating the use case RicercaTurista it selects and activates a function to modify data. 
2 Loads the data selected and displays them in a form allowing the change. 
3 Edit the fields in the form and submit. 
4 Verify the information and asks for confirmation of the change. Where the data is invalid or insufficient, the system activates the use case Errored. 
5 Confirm the operation. 
6. Stores the modified data selected account. 
Exit conditions - The system has been reporting the information required by the selected account Turista. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC16</id>
      <content>Use case name ELIMINAACCOUNTTURISTA 
Delete the account of a tourist from the system. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Tourists from the list obtained by activating the use case RicercaTurista will select and activate a feature for disposal. 
2 Asks for confirmation of the transaction. 
3 Confirm the operation. 
4 Delete the selected data. 
Exit conditions - The notification system has been elimination of selected accounts Turista. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC17</id>
      <content>Use case name MODIFICABANNER 
Changing the image of a banner ad. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Receives a list of turning points of the rest use case RicercaPuntiDiRistoro and select one from accessing the function of editing a banner. 
2 View the list of banner associated with the point of rest. 
3 Select a banner from the list and enter the editing functionality. 
4 Displays a form for the selection of an image. 
5 Select a picture and send the request to change the system. 
6. Check the characteristics of the inserted and asks for confirmation of the change of the banner. In the event that the inserted image is not valid, enable the use case Errored. 
7 Confirmation of the transaction change. 
8 Bookmark this new image for the selected banner. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the successful modification of the banner. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC18</id>
      <content>Use case name CONTROLLANUMEROBANNER 
Check if a point Refreshments included the maximum number of allowed banners to it. 
Partecipating 
Actor 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency wants to put a new banner 
Flow of events User System 
1. Load the data of the Convention of refreshment point and verify that the number of banners is less than the specified number of the current banner. If not checked, will end the operation input and displays a notification. 
2 Confirmation of the reading of the notification. 
3 Recovers the previous state. 
Exit conditions - The system returns control to the user interaction. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC19</id>
      <content>Use case name ELIMINABANNER 
Delete a banner ad associated with a refreshment bar on the computer. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Receives a list of turning points of the rest use case RicercaPuntiDiRistoro and select one from accessing the function of removal of the banner. 
2 View the list of banner associated with the point of rest. 
3 Select a banner from the list and enter the function of elimination. 
4 Displays a message confirming the deletion. 
5 Confirm the operation. 
6. Removes the banner. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the successful elimination of the selected banner. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC2</id>
      <content>Use case name INSERISCIBENECULTURALE 
Inserts a new cultural object in the system. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Activate the feature for the insertion of a new cultural good. 
2 Displays the corresponding form. 
3 Fill out the form with the data of the cultural and submit. 
4 Verify the data entered and asks for confirmation of the transaction. Where the data is invalid or insufficient, the system activates the use case Errored. 
5 Confirm the operation. 
6. Memorize your new cultural good. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the proper inclusion of the cultural. 
- Operator Agency cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
The system requirements will not accept duplicates cultural heritage.</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC20</id>
      <content>Use case name INSERISCIBANNER 
Inserting a new banner associated with a point of rest. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Receives a list of turning points of the rest use case RicercaPuntiDiRistoro and select one from the list and access to the function of inserting banners. 
2 Displays a form for the selection of an image. 
3 Select an image and sends the request for entering the system. 
4 Check the characteristics of the inserted, check that the number of banner did not exceed the maximum point of the restaurant and asks for confirmation of the insertion of the banner. In the event that the inserted image is not valid, enable the use case Errored. 

5 Confirm the operation of insertion. 
6. Remember the banners associated with the selected point of rest. 
Exit conditions - The notification about the insertion of new banner to the Refreshments selected. 
- The Operator Agency cancels the operation. 
- The point of eating has already entered the maximum number of banners allowed. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC21</id>
      <content>Use case name INSERISCINEWS 
Inserts a new news in the system. 
Participating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Activate the feature to insert a news. 
2 Displays the corresponding form. 
3 Fill out the form and submit. 
4 Verify the data entered and asks for confirmation of the transaction. Where the data is invalid or insufficient, the system activates the use case Errored. 
5 Confirm the operation of insertion. 
6. Stores the data of the new news. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the proper placement of the news. 
- The Operator Agency cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC22</id>
      <content>Use case name ELIMINANEWS 
Delete a news in the system. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Activate the function of elimination of a news. 
2 View all news in a form. 
3 Select a news from the list and submit the form. 
4 Asks for confirmation of the transaction. 
5 Confirm the deletion of the news. 
6. Delete the data news. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the successful elimination of the news. 
- The Operator Agency cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC23</id>
      <content>Use case name MODIFICANEWS 
Change data of a news on the computer. 
Participating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Activate the editing functionality of a news. 
2 View all news in a form. 
3 Select a news from the list and submit the form. 
4 Load the data of news and displays them in a form for editing. 
5 Change data in the form and submit. 
6. Check the modified information and asks for confirmation of the transaction. Where the data is invalid or insufficient, the system activates the use case Errored. 
7 Confirm the operation of changing the data news. 
8 Stores data modified news. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the successful amendment of news. 
- The Operator Agency cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC24</id>
      <content>Use case name VISUALIZZAFEEDBACK 
View all feedback for a particular site. 
Participating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. View the list of sites as a result of the use case RicercaSito, it selects and activates a function to view the feedback. 
2 Upload Site Feedback selected. 
Exit conditions - The system displays all feedback regarding the site selected. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC25</id>
      <content>Use case name VISUALIZZAREPORTSTATISTICI 
View statistical report relating to a selected location. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Activate the feature on the statistical report. 
2 Upload the list of places in the system and displays them in a form. 
3 Select a location and submit the form. 
4 Upload midsize site feedback obtained by activating the RicercaSito use case for the location selected. Prepare the statistical report. 
Exit conditions - The system displays the statistical report for the selected location. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC26</id>
      <content>Use case name MODIFICACOMMENTO 
Editing a comment by a feedback selected. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. View the list of sites as a result of the use case RicercaSito, it selects and activates a function of change in the selected comment. 
2 Upload feedback issued to that site and displays them in a form. 
3 Select a feedback from the list and submit the form. 
4 Displays a form for editing the comment of feedback selected. 
5 Edit the comment and submit the form. 
6. Verify the data entered and asks for confirmation of the change. Where the data is invalid or insufficient, the system activates the use case Errored. 
7 Confirm the operation. 
8 Remember the comment changed. 
Exit conditions - The notification system has been modified for the comment feedback selected. 
- Operator Agency cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC27</id>
      <content>Use case name RICERCASITO 
Searching for a specific site on the computer. 
Partecipating 
Actor 
Entry 
conditions 
Flow of events User System 
1. Activate the search functionality of a site. 
2 Show the form for research 
3 Fill in the form of research and submit 
4 Processing the request 
Exit conditions - The system returns a list of sites found 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
The system requirements should return the results within a time limit set</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC28</id>
      <content>Use case name ELIMINATAG 
Removes one or more search tags in the system. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Access the functionality to delete a tag. 
2 Research in the existing system, the tags and displays them in a form. 
3 Select one or more tags from the list and sends the request for deletion. 
4 Delete the selected search tag. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the successful elimination of selected tags. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC29</id>
      <content>Use case name ERRORETAGESISTENTE 
E 'was asked to enter a search tags already in the system. 
Participating 
Actor 
Entry 
conditions - He was asked to enter a search tags already in the system. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Notice the error message and asks for confirmation of its reading. 
2 Confirmation of the reading of the notification. 
3 Recovers the previous state. 
Exit conditions - The system returns control to the user interaction. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC3</id>
      <content>Use case name MODIFICABENECULTURALE 
Change data of a cultural object in the system. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. View the list of cultural goods as a result of the use case RicercaBeneCulturale, it selects and activates a function of change. 
2 Load the data of the cultural and displays the form for editing. 
3 Change data in the form and submit. 
4 Verify the data entered and asks for confirmation of the transaction. Where the data is invalid or insufficient, the system activates the use case Errored. 
5 Confirm the operation. 
6. Stores the modified data of the cultural. 
Exit conditions - The notification system has been changing the data of the cultural. 
- Operator Agency cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
The system requirements blocks of input controls in the form once we receive confirmation of the change to avoid multiple submissions before the end of the operation.</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC30</id>
      <content>Use case name INSERISCITAG 
Inserts a new tag search. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Access the functionality of inserting new tag search. 
2 Show the form for entering a tag. 
3 Fill out the form with the required information and submit. 
4 Verify the data entered and check if the tag is already present in the system. In the latter case the active use case ErroreTagEsistente. Instead, if the data is invalid or insufficient, the system activates the use case Errored. 
Exit conditions - The notification about the inclusion of the tag. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC31</id>
      <content>Use case name MODIFICAPASSWORD 
The Agency Operator chooses to change the password associated with your account 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
5 Choose to change your password by pressing the appropriate 
Button 
6. Upload the form to change the password associated with that work agency 
7 Change your password by entering the new choice and confirming 
8 Save your changes 
Exit conditions - The system confirms the success of Operation 
- Interruption of the connection to the server 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC32</id>
      <content>Use case name ERROREMODIFICAPASSWORD 
E 'was asked to enter a password but is not confirmed in a correct way. 
Participating 
Actor 
Entry 
conditions - It has been pressed the button to confirm the password change 
Flow of events User System 
4 Notify an error message. 
5 Confirmation of the reading of the notification. 
6. Back to change your password. 
Exit conditions - The system returns control to the user interaction. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC33</id>
      <content>Use case name REGISTRATION 
Requires the creation of a new system. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialized by Guest User 
Entry 
conditions - Guest User have access to the system. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Enable the logging feature. 
2 View the registration form. 
3 Fill out the form and submit. 
4 Verify the data entered and asks for confirmation of the transaction. Where the data is invalid or insufficient, the system activates the use case Errored. 
5 Confirm the operation. 
6. Create a new account with the data entered. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the successful operation of recording. 
- Guest User cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC34</id>
      <content>Use case name SEARCH 
Research and cultural heritage for all. 
Participating 
Actor initialized by Guest User 
Entry 
conditions - Guest User logs on. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Activate the search functionality. 
2 Displays the corresponding form. 
3 Fill out the form and submit. 
4 Gets the position dell'Utente Guest citing the case of use location and process research. 
Exit conditions - The system displays a list of sites that meet the search criteria. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC35</id>
      <content>Use case name LOGIN 
Ensures a registered user to access the system with the privileges that fall. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Registered User 
Entry 
conditions - A registered user has access to the system. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Activate the login feature. 
2 Displays the corresponding form. 
3 Fill out the form with login information and submit. 
4 Check the correctness of the data, if not corrected on the use case LoginErrato. 
Exit conditions - The system displays the area of work registered. 
- The registered user cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR .. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC36</id>
      <content>Use case name LOGINERRATO 
The data supplied for the login is incorrect. 
Participating 
Actor 
Entry 
Conditions - The data supplied for the login is incorrect. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Notice that the data entered for the login is not valid and asks for confirmation of the reading. 
2 Confirmation of the reading of the notification. 
3 Recovers the previous state. 
Exit conditions - The system returns control to the user interaction. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC37</id>
      <content>Use case name LOGOUT 
Ends the current session. 
Participating 
Actor initialization Registered User 
Entry 
conditions - A registered user has previously made a successful Login. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Access the functionality of disconnection from the system. 
2 Asks for confirmation of the transaction. 
3 Confirm the request for disconnection. 
4 Disconnects the Registered User. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the successful operation logout. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC38</id>
      <content>Use case name INSERISCIBANNER 
Inserting a new banner associated with the point of rest. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Operator Point Of Restaurants 
Entry 
conditions - The Point Of Restaurant Operator has successfully authenticated to the system. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Select the feature for the insertion of a new banner. 
2 Displays a form for the selection of an image. 
3 Select an image and sends the request for entering the system. 
4 Check the characteristics of the inserted, check that the number of banner did not exceed the maximum point of the restaurant and asks for confirmation of the insertion of the banner. In the event that the inserted image is not valid, enable the use case Errored. 

5 Confirm the operation of insertion. 
6. Remember the banners associated with the point of rest. 
Exit conditions - The notification about the insertion of new banner. 
- The Point Of Operator Restaurant cancels the operation. 
- The point of eating has already entered the maximum number of banners allowed. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC39</id>
      <content>Use case name MODIFICABANNER 
Changing the image of a banner ad. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Operator Point Of Restaurants 
Entry 
conditions - The Point Of Restaurant Operator has successfully authenticated to the system. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Select the editing functionality of the banner. 
2 View the list of banner associated with the point of rest. 
3 Select a banner from the list and enter the editing functionality. 
4 Displays a form for the selection of an image. 
5 Select a picture and send the request to change the system. 
6. Check the characteristics of the inserted and asks for confirmation of the change of the banner. In the event that the inserted image is not valid, enable the use case Errored. 
7 Confirmation of the transaction change. 
8 Bookmark this new image for the selected banner. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the successful modification of the banner. 
- The Point Of Operator Restaurant cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC4</id>
      <content>Use case name RICERCABENECULTURALE 
Returns the list of cultural objects in the system according to certain parameters. 
Partecipating 
Actor 
Entry 
conditions 
Flow of events User System 
1. Activate the search functionality of a cultural object. 
2 Show the form for research. 
3 Fill in the search form and submit. 
4 Processing the request. 
Exit conditions - The system returns a list of cultural goods that meet the search criteria. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
The system requirements should return the results within a set time.</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC40</id>
      <content>Use case name ELIMINABANNER 
Delete a banner ad associated with the point of rest. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Operator Point Of Restaurants 
Entry 
conditions - The Point Of Restaurant Operator has successfully authenticated to the system. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Select the feature for 'removal of the banner. 
2 View the list of banner associated with the point of rest. 
3 Select a banner from the list and enter the function of elimination. 
4 Displays a message confirming the deletion. 
5 Confirm the operation. 
6. Removes the banner. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the successful elimination of the selected banner. 
- The Point Of Operator Restaurant cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC41</id>
      <content>Use case name MODIFICAMENÙ 
Change the daily menu of a restaurant. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Operator Point Of Restaurants 
Entry 
conditions - The Point Of Restaurant Operator has successfully authenticated to the system. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Activate the editing functionality of the menu. 
2 Displays a form with seven days of the week. 
3 Select a day of the week and submit the form. 
4 Upload the data menu for the selected day and loads them into a form. 
5 Edit menu of the selected day and submit the form. 
6. Verify the data entered and asks for confirmation of the edit menu. Where the data are insufficient or invalid, the active use case Errored. 
7 Confirm the operation. 
8 Saves changes to the menu selected. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the successful modification of the menu. 
- Restaurant Point Of Operator cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC42</id>
      <content>Use case name ELIMINAMENÙ 
Delete a daily menu of a restaurant. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Operator Point Of Restaurants 
Entry 
conditions - The Point Of Restaurant Operator has successfully authenticated to the system. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Enable the functionality of deleting a menu. 
2 Displays a form containing the seven days of the week. 
3 Select a day of the week and submit the form. 
4 Calls to confirm the deletion. 
5 Confirm the operation. 
6. Delete the daily menu selection. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the successful elimination of the daily menu selection. 
- Restaurant Point Of Operator cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC43</id>
      <content>Use case name MODIFICADATIPUNTODIRISTORO 
Change data point associated refreshment. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Operator Point Of Restaurants 
Entry 
conditions - The Point Restaurant Operator has successfully authenticated to the system. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Enable the functionality of the information required by the point of rest. 
2 Upload data point Refreshments and displays them in a form. 
3 Change data in the form and submit. 
4 Verify the data entered and asks for confirmation of the change. Where the data is invalid or insufficient, the system activates the use case Errored. 
5 Confirm the operation. 
6. Stores the modified data of the point of rest. 
Exit conditions - The notification system has been changing the data point selected restaurants. 
- Restaurant Point Of Operator cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC44</id>
      <content>Use case name RICHIESTACONVENZIONE 
Require to conclude a Convention between the points of rest and the agency involved. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Operator Point Of Restaurants 
Entry 
conditions - The Point Of Restaurant Operator has successfully authenticated to the system. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Enable the functionality to request the Convention to the Agency. 
2 Displays a form for entering data of the Convention. 
3 Inserts the data in the form of the agreement and submit. 
4 Verify the data entered and asks for confirmation of the request. Where the data is invalid or insufficient, the system activates the use case Errored. 
5 Confirm the operation. 
6. Send the request to the Convention. 
Exit conditions - The notification about the call for the Convention to the Agency. 
- Restaurant Point Of Operator cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC45</id>
      <content>Use case name VISUALIZZASTATISTICHEPERSONALI 
Viewing statistics for Point Of Restaurants 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Operator Point Of Restaurants 
Entry 
conditions - The Point Of Restaurant Operator has successfully authenticated to the system. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Select the feature to display personal statistics. 
2 Displays a form that shows data for the statistics associated refreshment point. 
Exit conditions - The system displays the data on the screen. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server. 
Quality requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC46</id>
      <content>Use case name MODIFICAPREFERENZEDIRICERCA 
Edit your personal search preferences. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialized by Tourist 
Entry 
conditions - The Tourist has successfully authenticated to the system. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Access to functionality for the modification of personal search preferences. 
2 Upload your search preferences and displays them in a form. 
3 Edit the fields in the form and submit. 
4 Asks confirmation. 
5 Confirmation for changing search preferences. 
6. Memorize search preferences changed. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the successful modification of search preferences. 
- The Tourist cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC47</id>
      <content>Use case name MODIFICADATITURISTA 
Change data associated with your account. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialized by Tourist 
Entry 
Conditions - Tourism has successfully authenticated to the system. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Access to functionality for the modification of data. 
2 Loads the data and displays them in a form. 
3 Edit the fields in the form and submit. 
4 Check the modified information and asks for confirmation of the change. Where the data is invalid or insufficient, the system activates the use case Errored. 
5 Confirmation of the transaction change. 
6. Stores the modified data. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the successful modification of data. 
- The Tourist cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC48</id>
      <content>Use case name MODIFICAPREFERENZEGENERICHE 
Edit Preferences generic personal. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialized by Tourist 
Entry 
Conditions - Tourism has successfully authenticated to the system. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Access to functionality for the modification of generic personal preferences. 
2 Upload your preferences and the general view in a form. 
3 Edit the fields in the form and submit. 
4 Asks for confirmation of the change. 
5 Confirm the operation. 
6. Stores preferences changed. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the successful modification of general preferences. 
- The Tourist cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC49</id>
      <content>Use case name VISUALIZZASITIPREFERITI 
View the list of personal favorites. 
Participating 
Actor initialized by Tourist 
Entry 
conditions - The Tourist has successfully authenticated to the system. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Select the feature to display the list of personal favorites. 
2 Upload the list of bookmarks. 
Exit conditions - The system displays the list of bookmarks. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC5</id>
      <content>Use case name VISUALIZZASCHEDABENECULTURALE 
View the details of the selected cultural. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. View the list of cultural goods as a result of the use case RicercaBeneCulturale, it selects and activates a function to view the card. 
2 Loads the data for the selected cultural. 
Exit conditions - The system displays the details of the selected cultural. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC50</id>
      <content>Use case name VISUALIZZASITIVISITATI 
View the list of sites for which it has issued a feedback. 
Participating 
Actor initialized by Tourist 
Entry 
- conditions Turista has successfully authenticated to the system. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Select the feature to display the list of sites visited personal. 
2 Upload the list of sites for which the tourist has issued a Feedback 
Exit conditions - The system displays a list of sites visited. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC51</id>
      <content>Use case name INSERISCISITONEIPREFERITI 
Inserts a site selected in the list of bookmarks. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialized by Tourist 
Entry 
conditions - The tourist card is in a particular site. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Activate the feature for the insertion of the selected site from the bookmarks. 
2 Prompt the inclusion 
3 Confirm the input. 
4 Inserts the selected site in the list of bookmarks. 
Exit conditions - The notification about the insertion site to favorites 
- Interruption of connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC52</id>
      <content>Use case name ELIMINASITODAIPREFERITI 
Tourism delete a site from the list of bookmarks. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialized by Tourist 
Entry 
conditions - The tourist card is in a particular site. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Choose to remove your site from the list of bookmarks by specific features. 
2 Prompt removal 
3 Confirm the removal. 
4 Removes the selected site from the list of bookmarks. 
Exit conditions - The notification system has been removed from the site bookmarks. 
- The Tourist cancel the operation 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC53</id>
      <content>Use case name INSERISCIFEEDBACK 
Inserts a feedback for the selected site. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialized by Tourist 
Entry 
conditions - The tourist card is in a particular site. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Activate the feature on the issue of feedback. 
2 Verify that the visitor has not already issued a feedback for the site and displays a form for entering the feedback for the selected site. In case the visitor has already issued a feedback for the site selected, activates the use case FeedbackGiàRilasciato. 
3 Fill out the form, selecting one vote and inserting a comment, then submit. 
4 Verify the data entered and confirm the cheide. Where the data is invalid or insufficient, the system activates the use case Errored. 
5 Confirming the issue of feedback. 
6. Remember feedback and inserts the selected site in the list of sites visited. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the successful combination of feedback to the site 
- The Tourist cancel the operation 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC54</id>
      <content>Use case name MODIFICACOMMENTO 
Edit the comment previously issued. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialized by Tourist 
Entry 
- Tourist conditions is in the details of a particular site. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Choose to change the comment on the feedback for the site issued by the appropriate functionality. 
2 Verify the data entered and asks for confirmation of the change. Where the data is invalid or insufficient, the system activates the use case Errored. 
3 Confirm the change of the comment. 
4 Edit commentary on selected feedback 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the alterations of the comment 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC55</id>
      <content>Use case name FEEDBACKGIA'RILASCIATO 
E 'already been issued with a feedback for the selected site. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization 
Entry 
conditions - E 'already been issued with a feedback for the selected site. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Notification that the user has already issued a feedback for the site and cancel the operation to insert a new feedback. 
2 Confirmation of the reading of the notification. 
3 Recovers the previous state. 
Exit conditions - The system returns control to the user interaction. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC56</id>
      <content>Use case name LOCALIZATION 
Returns the current position of the tourist. 
Partecipating 
Actor System initialization 
Entry 
conditions - E 'began a search or an advanced search. 
Flow of events Gps System 
1. The system requires the data for the position. 
2 The GPS calculates the position of the tourist. 
3 The system is on hold until the data of the position. 
Exit conditions - The system receives the position of the tourist. 
- The position of the tourist is not detectable by GPS. 
Quality 
The GPS requirements into the transaction in more than 5 seconds.</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC57</id>
      <content>Use case name RICERCAAVANZATA 
The tourist searching for a site using the potential offered by the Advanced Search. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialized by Tourist 
Entry 
conditions - The Tourist has successfully authenticated to the system. 
Flow of events User System 
1. Enable the advanced search feature from your personal area. 
2 View the advanced search form. 
3 Fill in the form of advanced search and submit. 
4 Gets the position of relying on the tourist event of the use location and process the request. 
Exit conditions - The system displays a list of results. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
The system requirements into the transaction in more than 15 seconds.</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC58</id>
      <content>Use case name VISUALIZZASCHEDASITO 
View the details of a particular site. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialized by Tourist 
Entry 
conditions - The Tourist has successfully authenticated to the system and is located in one of the following areas: Research Results, List of Sites Visited Sites and List of Favorites 
Flow of events User System 
1. Select the function for displaying the card on a site chosen. 
2 Upload data from the database. 
Exit conditions - The system displays the details of the selected site. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC6</id>
      <content>Use case name ELIMINAPUNTODIRISTORO 
Delete a refreshment from the system. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Operator Agency. 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. View a list of points of rest as a result of the use case RicercaBeneCulturale, it selects and activates a function of elimination. 
2 Asks for confirmation of the transaction. 
3 Confirm the deletion. 
4 Deletes the selected point of rest. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the successful elimination of the point of rest. 
- Operator Agency cancels the operation. 
- Interruption ETOUR connection to the server. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC7</id>
      <content>Use case name ATTIVACONVENZIONE 
Convention active request by a refreshment point. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The Agency is in the form of a designated point of rest. 

Flow of events User System 
1. Enable the activation function of the Convention. 
2 Load the data request of the Convention from the point of rest and displays the corresponding form. 
3 Check the data of the agreement and decide for activation. 
4 Asks for confirmation of the activation. 
5 Confirm the operation. 
6. Processing the request. 
Exit conditions - The system shall notify the activation of the convention. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
requirements</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC8</id>
      <content>Use case name MODIFICADATIPUNTODIRISTOROAGENZIA 
Edit the data pertaining to a designated point of rest. 
Partecipating 
Actor initialization Agency Operator 
Entry 
Operator conditions - The agency has logged. 
Flow of events User System 
1. View a list of points of rest as a result of the use case RicercaPuntoDiRistoro, it selects an active and functional data changes. 
2 Upload data from the point of rest and displays the form of change. 
3 Change data in the form and submit. 
4 Verify the data entered in form and asks for confirmation of the transaction. Where the data is invalid or insufficient, the system activates the use case Errored. 
5 Confirm the operation. 
6. Stores the modified data of the point of rest. 
Exit conditions - The system has been reporting the information required by the point of rest. 
- Operator Agency cancels the operation. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 
Quality 
The system requirements blocks of input controls in the form once we receive confirmation of the change to avoid multiple submissions before the end of the operation.</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC9</id>
      <content>Use case name RICERCAPUNTIDIRISTORO 
Returns the list of points of rest in the system according to certain parameters. 
Partecipating 
Actor 
Entry 
conditions 
Flow of events User System 
1. Activate the search functionality of a point of rest. 
2 Show the form for research. 
3 Fill in the search form and submit. 
4 Processing the request. 
Exit conditions - The system returns a list of points of rest which meet your search criteria. 
- Interruption of the connection to the server ETOUR. 

Quality requirements - The system performs the operation in 15 seconds maximum</content>
      <parent_id/>
    </artifact>
  </artifacts>
</artifacts_collection>
